{
    "id": "2b55501557d54927a9ec40c6fa5f925b",
    "title": "Much, Many, A Lot, A Lot Of",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "How ............................ brothers and sisters do you have?",
            "description": "Use many with plural nouns in questions and negatives.",
            "answers": [
                "many",
                "much",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "c7286fcb8b1e466b9bf3333ceda5d92e"
        },
        {
            "question": "She doesn't have .............................. money.",
            "description": "Either much or a lot of is possible here.",
            "answers": [
                "much",
                "many",
                "a lot of"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "97f44089a8b74f568417133a52f963a5"
        },
        {
            "question": "He did ............................. for me when he was alive.",
            "description": "Much is not normally used in affirmative sentences.",
            "answers": [
                "much",
                "a lot",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "fef8395533f9425ea4d8eef97e310627"
        },
        {
            "question": "She doesn't read ................................",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "many",
                "much",
                "a lot of"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "963a7f342645490fbe51ab390abb7388"
        },
        {
            "question": "She has ................................. friends.",
            "description": "Many is not normally used in affirmative sentences. ",
            "answers": [
                "a lot of",
                "much",
                "many",
                "a lot"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "1380be8c54db45599de10cb10540741e"
        },
        {
            "question": "There aren't .............................. apples on the tree.",
            "description": "Either many or a lot of is possible here.  A lot of can be used in affirmative, negative and interrogative sentences. ",
            "answers": [
                "many",
                "much",
                "a lot of"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "8a70e2151a434e558a7c92efc2bd9622"
        },
        {
            "question": "I have been watching ............................... movies recently.",
            "description": "Many is not normally used in affirmative sentences. Either lots of or a lot of can be used here.",
            "answers": [
                "a lot of",
                "lots of",
                "many"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "a7e2f369809e47878fc740a3bd5a7186"
        },
        {
            "question": "I ate ................................ food.",
            "description": "A lot cannot be used before a noun. Use a lot of.",
            "answers": [
                "a lot",
                "a lot of",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "9e76e3dc8a7046c8bd86cee38cb603e0"
        },
        {
            "question": "....................................... social problems are caused by poverty.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "A lot of",
                "Much",
                "A lot"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "efacab2cbd8b460695f809c218f394cd"
        },
        {
            "question": "Her condition hasn't improved ................................",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "much",
                "many",
                "a lot"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "7814e49609d446e1b47deac6321ad00d"
        },
        {
            "question": "I didn't know ................................ people at the party.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "many",
                "much",
                "a lot of"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "85d8c125fc8745bca34208dc94b1afa8"
        },
        {
            "question": "I have been partying ............................... these days.",
            "description": "A lot of is used before a noun.",
            "answers": [
                "a lot",
                "a lot of",
                "much"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "5b5203daffaa4d90b7887aa3b4ad5091"
        }
    ]
}